CURRICULUM VITAE

Rushdi Basim

13701 Winding Oak Cir, APT 201 Centreville, VA 20121

Cell phone: 619-394-1399, Email: rushdihijab@gmail.com

SUMMARY:

Two years experience of customer service and sales expert who identifies customer needs and delivers effective solutions to problems. Three years of highly organized and detail focused Full-Charge Bookkeeper with track record of accurately and efficiently supporting overall accounting activities.

EDUCATION:

Master of Business Administration, National University, San Diego, CA (2015-2017) Bachelor of Laws, Applied Science University, Jordan, Amman (2009-2012)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Classic Interior Consignments, Manassas, VA

Sales and customer service, January 2018 – Present

Responsibilities include selling furniture, budgeting, recruiting and training new employees, communicating with home builders to supply the store with model homes furniture, managing displays, maintaining supplies and providing customer support.

Jafa Tax and Accounting Experts, Falls Church, VA

Part time Bookkeeper, May 2018 – March 2019

Managed financial transactions and record keeping with strict attention to detail. Reconciled and balanced accounts compiled statistical reports for management, and generated invoices and monthly statements.

Time between July 2015 to December 2017 (see above – Education)

Baghdad Company for Gas Turbines Ltd, Jordan

Accountant, June 2012 – July 2015

Calculating and preparing monthly adjusting journal entry with records of bank fees, interest income and outgoing wire transfers.

CV continued:

- Keeping and updating all accounting records and forwarding the detail to the senior management as and when required.
- Resolving discrepancies if found in the bank records of payable transactions and bank listing.
- Comprehensive knowledge of accounting and auditing principles, A/P, A/R, payroll, general ledger postings, invoicing, taxation issues, and regulatory compliance guidelines.
- Sales and customer service.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS:

Microsoft Office, Word, Excel, PowerPoint and QuickBooks Extensive knowledge in accounting. Excellent writing and interpersonal skills. Accounts receivable and accounts payable

OTHERS:

Will be furnished upon request